[
      {
        "question": "How many Chinese men start to smoke before the age of 20?",
        "options": ["one-third", "two-thirds", "half", "all of them"],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the word \"those men\" in paragraph 2 refer to?",
        "options": [
            "Men who smoke under the age of 20",
            "Men who smoke above the age of 20",
            "Men who give up smoking",
            "Men who smoke in public"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "By 2030, how many men in China may die from smoking every year?",
        "options": [
            "one million",
            "two million",
            "three million",
            "four million"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "In many areas of China, when do men usually smoke?",
        "options": [
            "Before a meal",
            "After a meal",
            "Before they go to sleep",
            "When they get up"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "According to WHO, only ________ of Chinese adults can list bad effects of smoking.",
        "options": ["one-third", "one-fourth", "one-fifth", "a half"],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Beijing\" refers to ....................",
        "options": [
            "China",
            "The city of Beijing",
            "The Chinese government",
            "People who live in Beijing"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Richard Peto's attitude toward smoking in China?",
        "options": [
            "He doesn't believe that people will give up smoking",
            "He is disappointed with the Chinese government.",
            "He thinks that people possibly stop smoking if they see reasons.",
            "He is sure about the rise of future deaths in China."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following words does the word \"hamper\" have closest meaning to?",
        "options": ["basket", "assist", "prohibit", "restrict"],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the writer's purpose?",
        "options": [
            "To argue over smoking policy in China",
            "To support smoking in China",
            "To warn and prevent smoking in China",
            "To report the result ofa research paper"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the writer imply about Chinese government?",
        "options": [
            "They do not want to stop people from smoking",
            "They have tried to stop people from smoking in public but with little success.",
            "They have tried to close tobacco companies.",
            "They do not care about smoking."
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    }
]